hey it's Rob with the schedule update
all right weekdays are protect content
Sundays and weekdays are protect content
except for yoga at 9:00 join me for yoga
chill music uh potentially a little bit
of conversation Q you know Q&A about
yoga 9:00 a.m. every day um that's not
going anywhere we're going to do the
yoga tradition of taking Saturday off so
Saturday will be when we do IRL content
we're going to do a lot of biking on
Saturday uh road trips and stuff like
that so that means no IRL content during
the week which is a change um it just
can't fit it in I got to work and so
home lab content specifically for those
of you who want to help build out your
home lab you can come watch me build out
my home lab Friday
afternoon uh and for those of you who
want to do the beginner boost and you
want to be here for the in the live
Studio H for that that's going to be uh
Sunday morning this this schedule starts
November 2nd when we head in when we go
into the to Daylight Savings Time and
everything so hopefully that gets you
guys caught up um please join me please
join me for uh random twitch Tech
content during the week this is not on
the calendar uh I am streaming on
average uh 3 to six hours a day uh of
tech content on Twitch that only is
saved as a B on Twitch not most of the
time it doesn't get published YouTube
sometimes it does so if you want to be
here for that you can come you can come
see that if I have something interesting
that I've discovered I'll summarize it
and put it on YouTube so that's that's
where we are hopefully that gives you uh
a sense of what's going on and and um
come join us